Resources

[Blog

Get insights, best practices, and thought leadership straight from the experts](https://www.admarketplace.com/blog)[Infographics

Take a visual deep dive into the latest industry trends and data](https://www.admarketplace.com/infographics)[Case Studies

Discover how we’ve empowered some of the world’s largest brands to achieve greater success](https://www.admarketplace.com/case-studies)[Insights & Research

Stay up-to-date on all the latest learnings and insights to optimize your campaign performance](https://www.admarketplace.com/insights-research)

#### Featured

[

**Intent-based Media**

Unwrap Search Advertising Success During the Most Wonderful Time of the Year

Learn more](https://www.admarketplace.com/blog/unwrap-search-advertising-success-during-the-most-wonderful-time-of-the-year)[

**Open Web Search**

Just Browsing: Shaping Consumer Intent with Media Opportunities on Open Web Privacy Browsers

Learn more](https://www.admarketplace.com/blog/just-browsing-shaping-consumer-intent-with-media-opportunities-on-open-web-privacy-browsers)

About

[

News

You heard it here first – all the latest AMP news, updates, and announcements](https://www.admarketplace.com/news)[

Employee Spotlight

Honoring the talent, attributes, and wins of the incredible individuals that make up Team AMP](https://www.admarketplace.com/employee-spotlight)[

IMPACT

adMarketplace's annual, premier search advertising conference](https://www.admarketplace.com/impact-2024-conference)

[Our Story

From humble beginnings to predominant adtech player, brush up on adMarketplace’s history](https://www.admarketplace.com/our-story)[

Culture & Careers

We're hiring!

Discover the culture that powers our success and browse our open roles for your next big opportunity](https://www.admarketplace.com/culture-and-careers)

#### Featured

[

**News**

Mozilla Expands Partnership with adMarketplace

Learn more](https://www.admarketplace.com/blog/mozilla-expands-partnership-with-admarketplace-on-the-journey-to-protect-consumer-privacy-while-delivering-value-to-advertisers)[

**Spotlight**

Transforming Marketing Expertise into Product Innovation

Learn more](https://www.admarketplace.com/blog/marketing-leader-to-senior-product-manager-transforming-marketing-expertise-into-product-innovation-transitioning-from-a-career)

Contact us
----------

I am a/an

Advertiser

Publisher

Agency

First Name

Last Name

Work email

Title

Company

Thank you! Your submission has been received!

Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.

Oops!
=====

Please enter a business email

Resources

[

Blog

Get insights, best practices, and thought leadership straight from the experts.](https://www.admarketplace.com/blog)[

Case Studies

Discover how we've empowered some of the world's largest brands to achieve greater success.](https://www.admarketplace.com/case-studies)[

Infographics

Take a visual deep dive into the latest industry trends and data.](https://www.admarketplace.com/infographics)[

Insights & Research

Stay up-to-date on all the latest learnings and insights to optimize your campaign performance](https://www.admarketplace.com/insights-research)

About

[

Our Story

From humble beginnings to predominant adtech player, brush up on adMarketplace’s history.](https://www.admarketplace.com/our-story)[

News

You heard it here first—all the latest AMP news, updates, and announcements.](https://www.admarketplace.com/news)[

Culture & Careers

Discover the culture that powers our successes and browse our open roles for your next big opportunity.](https://www.admarketplace.com/culture-and-careers)[

Employee Spotlight

Honoring the talents, attributes, and wins of the incredible individuals that make up Team AMP.](https://www.admarketplace.com/employee-spotlight)

Contact us
----------

I am a/an

Advertiser

Publisher

Agency

First Name

Last Name

Work email

Title

Company

Thank you! Your submission has been received!

Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.

Oops!
=====

Please enter a business email

Privacy Policy
--------------

**Updated:** September 05, 2023

This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) informs about Personal Information processed  
through adMarketplace, Inc.’s ("adMarketplace’s") products and services (“Service(s)”)  
which is for the purpose of providing certain advertising related services for our  
Customers.

This Privacy Policy also informs about information collected from this website,  
[www.admarketplace.com](http://www.admarketplace.com/), which serves two basic functions. First, it has  
information about our Services as well as online advertising generally. Second, it is a portal  
for adMarketplace publishers and advertisers ("Customer(s)") to access certain restricted,  
Customer-only materials through secure log-in.

This Privacy Policy does not relate to Customer business information shared with us (e.g.,  
billing or contact details). As well, it does not relate to information shared by employees or  
other staff, or by applicants for positions with our company. You may reach your business  
or HR contact for inquiries related to such information).

**1\. Our Commitment to Data Privacy**
--------------------------------------

It is of critical importance to us to keep the information we collect secure. adMarketplace is  
also committed to protecting the privacy of consumers and observes compliance with  
applicable laws, including the EU’s and United Kingdom’s Data Protection Regulation  
("GDPR") and various state privacy laws in the United States including CCPA (“US Privacy  
Laws”) and relevant laws of other countries and/or regions, collectively referred to as  
“Data Protection Laws”. As our practices evolve, this Privacy Policy may be revised to  
reflect those changes. Notice of such amendments will be posted as an updated notice on  
this website. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically in order to keep up to date with  
any modifications.

**2\. Who is adMarketplace?**
-----------------------------

adMarketplace is a provider of Services that enable our Customers to reach consumers as  
they search for or indicate intent to learn more about or engage with our Customers’  
products or services. Our Services do not use **Personal Information** to track, target, or  
otherwise profile consumers across unrelated websites, apps, devices, platforms or  
properties (collectively referred to herein as ‘**Sites**’). Personal Information (also referred to  
as Personal Data) means any information related to an identifiable person and includes IP  
addresses, cookie identifiers and device identifiers.

(Personal Information is distinct from **Personally Identifiable Information (PII)** which is  
information that on its own is able to identify, contact, or locate an individual. An example  
of PII is an individual’s email address. adMarketplace Services do not collect, process, or  
use PII).

The corporate entity that decides how and for what purpose we process information (the  
legal basis for processing) is:

adMarketplace, Inc.,  
90 Park Ave,  
11th Floor New York, NY 10016 USA  
Tel. +1 212 925 2022  
Email: [privacy@admarketplace.com](mailto:privacy@admarketplace.com)

**3\. Purposes of and Legal Bases for Processing of Personal Information**
--------------------------------------------------------------------------

We process Personal Information as set out below:

a.  If you are an internet user visiting one of our Customer’s Sites: On behalf of our  
Customer, we may process Personal Information in order to deliver ads to the Site  
you visit. To illustrate, our technology shows ads in the following ways:

* Pre-search: we show tiles (display ads) for different trusted brands who are our  
    Customers, below the search box
* During search: while a search request is being typed, we may show links that  
    allow you to directly navigate to the brand Site(s) and "skip" having to go to  
    a search engine results page
* Post-search: we may include links to brand Sites within search results
* Native Search: we may include links to brand Sites within editorial, informational  
    or consumer-generated content
* Push Notifications: if you have expressly opted-in, we may show notifications  
    from brands at a specific time of day to your desktop, mobile or other device
* Auto-complete Search: we may provide auto-complete feature and/or redirect  
    your mistyped or misspelled brand searches to the actual brand domain you may  
    have intended to type, and thus bypass parked pages

b.  We process Personal Information collected from our Customer’s Sites on their  
behalf to deliver Services. Our bases for processing when you visit Customer Sites is  
as follows:

* For display of advertising: we are a processor or service provider to the  
    Publisher who has legitimate interest or obtained consent from you when you  
    visited their Site, to display advertising
* When a consumer clicks on an ad (creative) displayed on the site of our  
    publisher customer, we may operate as processor or service provider to the  
    advertiser whose ad (creative) the consumer chose to click
* In order to improve our Services and to develop new services or features for our  
    Customers
* In order to maintain security, identify fraud and similar misconduct
* In order to understand trends in how users react to particular types of  
    advertisements or offers
* In order to provide insights and reporting back to Customers, such as statistical  
    reporting in connection with the activity on Sites, optimization of the location of  
    ad placement, ad performance, reach and frequency metrics, and billing
* In order to resolve or fix technical issues or problems and to respond to user  
    inquiries and requests
* In order to comply with legal obligation - in some cases, we may have a legal  
    obligation to collect, maintain, or disclose personal information about you in  
    relation to the Services

c.   If you are a visitor to our Site ([admarketplace.com](http://admarketplace.com/)): any processing of Personal  
Information is as follows:

* To process the information voluntarily shared with us when you contact us  
    (with inquiries, for example), and
* For operational purposes (relating to your device type, for example), to enable,  
    improve, or otherwise manage the delivery of content on our Sites

**4\. What are the Categories of Personal Information we Collect for our Services?**
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

1. **Search** information such as commercial search terms (keywords) entered into a  
    search box
2. **Online Identifiers**, including browser and device information such as your device’s  
    Internet protocol (“IP”) address, unique device identifiers such as advertising,  
    hardware or operating system device identifiers (e.g., IDFA for iOS and AAID for  
    Android), information about the type of Internet browser, and general geographic  
    information, and in some cases, cookie IDs. Cookies are text files with a small piece  
    of data sent from a website and stored in a user’s web browser or pixels (graphics  
    embedded in ad content to reflect an interaction with an ad on a Customer’s website  
    – pixels work similarly to cookies). You can find more information about different  
    types of cookies at [allaboutcookies.org](http://allaboutcookies.org/)
3. **Commercial Information**, including products and services you may have  
    interacted with on the Sites of our Customers
4. **Internet Activity**, including information about your actions on the Sites of our  
    Customers, such as information related to the Site you are viewing; visit dates and  
    times; the website you came from before, and visited after you clicked on an ad; ad  
    engagement data
5. **Advertisement performance information for ads served**, viewed or clicked on,  
    such as information about the type of ad, the online location where the ad was  
    served, whether it was clicked on, and the products and offers viewed while  
    browsing or searching
6. **Inferences** drawn by us or our Customers (or partners of our Customers or who  
    work with us) such as age range, demographics, and product interests

As with any information we collect or process, we do not use any Personal Information  
collected or shared with us to track, target, or otherwise profile consumers across  
unrelated Sites.

**5\. What are Categories of Personal Information collected our website?**
--------------------------------------------------------------------------

1. **User Provided Information** - on our website’s "contact us" pages, fields are  
    provided so that customers or others interested in our Services can input contact  
    details. We collect this information so that we can respond to the information sent to  
    us
2. **Online Identifiers** - in order to maintain and manage our website, we record  
    information such as IP addresses, page views and clicks, and cookies for gathering  
    website statistics.

**6\. Statement about Sensitive Information and about Deidentified Information**
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

We do not collect any personal information defined as “sensitive personal information”  
under CCPA or US Privacy Laws, nor any “special categories” of personal data per GDPR.

The Services are not intended to process personal information of children under the age of  
16 and we do not knowingly collect, sell, share, or process any personal information from  
children under the age of 16. If you, as a parent or guardian, believe that your child under  
the age of 16 has interacted with our Services and caused us to unknowingly collect  
their personal information, please contact us and we will use our best efforts to identify  
and remove their information to the extent it is in our records.

In addition to our personal information collection and processing, we may collect, create,  
process, disclose and store information that is not considered personal information  
because it is not identifiable to a particular individual, such as sets of aggregate data,  
metadata, and other generalized information about online browsing, usage and  
interactions, as well as de-identified information that does not reveal your identity. We do  
not attempt to re-identify or associate such information to you, and we retain the right to  
use and disclose such information in any manner permitted by applicable law.

**7\. What are the Sources of Personal Information?**
-----------------------------------------------------

1. **Information received through** **technologies:** When you interact with or on our  
    Customer’s Sites, depending on the applicable laws in your location, we may receive  
    the categories of information provided above, through technologies such as APIs or  
    cookies
2. **Information we receive from our Customers or their data providers:** Our  
    Customers may supply us with personal information about consumers, to the extent  
    they have confirmed that they have sufficient authority to provide this information  
    to us, in order to deliver more relevant content, advertising, products or services.  
    Such processing is subject to those Customers’ privacy policies and the legal terms  
    under which they collected the relevant personal information

**8\. Personal information disclosures**
----------------------------------------

When we disclose personal information, we disclose it to the following categories of  
recipients for the following business and commercial purposes:

1. to our Customers or their designated third-party representatives as part of our Services
2. to technology, infrastructure, operations and other service providers to help support  
    the infrastructure necessary to provide the Services
3. We may also disclose information about you:

1. if we are required to do so by law or legal process, including in response to a valid  
    request from law enforcement authorities or other government officials
2. when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or  
    financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal  
    activity
3. if necessary to protect our legal rights or the legal rights of another individual or  
    entity
4. in connection with a corporate reorganization or a sale or transfer of all or a portion  
    of our business or asset, or
5. to any other person with your consent to the disclosure.

**Selling and sharing personal information**
--------------------------------------------

We do NOT “sell,” “share,” process or disclose your personal information for targeted  
advertising or otherwise as those terms are defined under applicable U.S. Privacy Laws.

**9\. Security**
----------------

adMarketplace applies commercially reasonable physical, technical and organizational  
security measures to protect information from unauthorized access, corruption or loss.  
These include storing information in databases which are protected by security measures  
such as password protection, multi-factor authentication, and encryption using Transport  
Layer Security technology (TLS). However, no system can be completely secure, and we  
make no guarantees as to security of information transmitted through our Services or our  
own website ([adMarketplace.com](http://admarketplace.com/))

**10\. Third Parties we work with**
-----------------------------------

We may use processors or service providers for our business purposes (e.g. for data storage  
or fraud detection); when we do so, we obligate these services to comply with our Privacy  
and Security policy requirements and the Privacy Shield Principles for onward data  
transfers, including obligations to provide the same level of protection that we afford for  
transferred data.

The adMarketplace website may contain links to third party websites; please be aware that  
we do not endorse and are not responsible for the privacy practices of those websites. If  
you follow a link to those websites, you should read their privacy notice and terms and  
conditions to discern their practices.

**11\. International Data Transfers**
-------------------------------------

For EU and UK data transfers to entities in countries that have not been deemed to provide  
an adequate level of protection by the European Commission, we use approved contracts,  
such as the EU Standard Contractual Clauses for the transfer of personal data to Third  
Countries pursuant to Regulation (EU) 2016/679 in accordance with Commission  
Implementing Decision (EU) 2021/914 of 4 June 2021 and the United Kingdom’s  
International Data Transfer Addendum to the EU Commission Standard Contractual  
Clauses, in force 21 March 2022, as appropriate and additional safeguards where required.

adMarketplace complies with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF), the  
UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework  
(Swiss-U.S. DPF) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce.  adMarketplace has  
certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy  
Framework Principles (EU-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal  
data received from the European Union in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and from the  
United Kingdom (and Gibraltar) in reliance on the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF.  
adMarketplace has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the  
Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard  
to the processing of personal data received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-U.S. DPF.  
If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles  
and/or the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles, the Principles shall govern.  To learn more about the  
Data Privacy Framework (DPF) program, and to view our certification, please visit  
[https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/)/.

In compliance with the EU-US DPF Principles, adMarketplace commits to resolve complaints  
about our collection or use of your personal information.  EU or UK individuals with questions  
concerning our DPF policy may directed them to [privacy@admarketplace.com](mailto:privacy@admarketplace.com). If we have  
not been able to satisfactorily resolve the issue, then, you may submit your complaint to  
JAMS using this link: [https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-data-privacy-framework](https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-data-privacy-framework).  
JAMS is adMarketplace’s designated DPF dispute resolution provider.

For transfers of personal data from non-EU/UK countries where international data transfers are  
limited or restricted, we comply with the relevant applicable laws to legitimize such transfers.

adMarketplace is responsible for processing personal information it receives under the DPF  
and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. adMarketplace  
shall remain liable under the Principles if its agent processes such personal information in a  
manner inconsistent with the Principles unless it shows it is not responsible for the event  
giving rise to the matter.

**12\. Retention of Data**
--------------------------

We retain Personal Information for only as long as necessary for the business purpose of  
the processing. Personal Information collected by our Services is retained for sixty-one days  
in the normal course. Aggregated and anonymized may be retained for a longer period for  
statistical purposes and for reporting to and billing our customers.

**13\. Your Privacy Rights under Data Protection Laws**
-------------------------------------------------------

Description of your privacy rights

You may have certain rights regarding your personal information, based on applicable Data  
Protection Laws, which may include the following:

1. To know about our processing of your personal information/data – you may request  
    that we provide you:  
    
2. Confirmation as to whether we are processing your personal information/data
3. The categories of personal information we process about you
4. The purposes of processing, including our business or commercial purpose for  
    collecting, selling, or sharing your personal information
5. The categories of sources from which we collected your personal information
6. The categories of personal information we disclosed for a business purpose and the  
    categories of recipients to whom we disclosed it, especially international recipients
7. The categories of personal information we sold or shared with third parties for  
    targeted or cross context behavioral advertising and the categories of third parties  
    to whom we sold or shared it
8. The existence of any automated processing
9. Expected retention periods.
10. To Access your personal information/data portability – You may request that we send  
    you (or another organization, under certain conditions) a copy of your personal data in  
    our possession, in a readily usable and portable format.
11. To Rectify/Correct inaccurate personal information the information we hold about you  
    – You may request that we correct personal information you believe is inaccurate or  
    complete any information you believe is incomplete;
12. To Erase/Delete your personal information – You may request that we delete your  
    personal information under certain conditions or subject to certain legal exceptions;
13. To Restrict/Limit our processing of your personal information – You may request that  
    we restrict our processing of your personal information, under certain circumstances;
14. To Object to our Processing of your personal information – You may object to our  
    processing of your personal information, under certain circumstances;
15. To Opt-out of certain disclosures of your personal information that may be considered  
    selling or sharing for the purposes of targeted or cross-context behavioral advertising;
16. To Withdraw your Consent – You may request to withdraw your consent for processing  
    that is based on your consent;
17. To Not Be Subject to Discrimination for exercising your rights – We will not discriminate  
    against you for exercising any of your privacy rights by denying you goods or services,  
    charging you or suggesting you may receive different prices or rates for goods or  
    services, or providing you a different level or quality of goods or services if you exercise  
    your rights.
18. To Lodge a Complaint – We appreciate the opportunity to address any complaint you  
    may have about our processing of your personal information or handling of your rights  
    request, so please direct any concerns to us via email at [privacy@admarketplace.com](mailto:privacy@admarketplace.com).  
    Regardless, you have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our  
    collection and use of your personal information. Contact details for data protection  
    authorities in the European Economic Area are available here:  
    [https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/about-edpb/members\_en#member-be](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/about-edpb/members_en#member-be), and for the  
    UK’s ICO here: [https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/)**.**

For Personal Information collected via our Services, you should contact the relevant  
Customer (Site publisher or advertiser) that is the business controlling or controller of such  
information.

In regard to Personal Information collected from our own website ([adMarketplace.com](http://admarketplace.com/)),  
you can withdraw your consent by contacting us. In regard to Europe Data, you may also  
contact our DPO at [dpo@admarketplace.com](mailto:dpo@admarketplace.com) or [privacy@admarketplace.com](mailto:privacy@admarketplace.com) .

**14\. California requirements**
--------------------------------

California residents have certain rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act:  
[Click here](https://www.admarketplace.com/california-consumer-privacy-act-ccpa) to read additional disclosures required under CCPA.

Shine the light

California law permits California residents to annually request certain details about how  
their information is shared with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.  We do  
not share your information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**
----------------------------------

adMarketplace reserves the right to change or replace this Privacy Policy at any time to  
reflect any changes in our privacy practices or updates to applicable laws. When we update  
our Privacy Policy, we will take appropriate measures to inform you, consistent with the  
significance of the changes we make. We will obtain your consent to any material Privacy  
Policy changes that affect your personal information if and where this is required by  
applicable data protection laws. Any changes or replacement will be posted on our website  
related to this Privacy Policy and located here. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy  
on a regular basis.

**Contact us**
--------------

For any questions about our privacy practices, you may contact our data protection officer  
and privacy team by email here: [privacy@admarketplace.com](mailto:privacy@admarketplace.com), or via:

Our postal address:  
adMarketplace Inc.  
90 Park Ave,  
New York, NY 10016 USA  
Tel. +1 212 925 2022

By Audience

By Product

Measurement

Privacy

Resources

About

Our locations

90 Park Ave  
Floor 11  
New York, NY 10016

60 London Wall  
London, UK EC2M 5TQ

Subscribe to our Blog

Thank you! Your submission has been received!

Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.

© Copyright 2024 adMarketplace

Our website USES cookies. By continuing navigating, we assume your permission to deploy cookies as detailed in our [Privacy Policy.](https://www.admarketplace.com/privacy-policy)
